It's a departure in that evening of last
year,
great pleasure,
find the point of making a formula
that there are some
who could also be dung
beetles
to point out as well in his wine,
simply we have paradoxes for each of you, you
are mobilized for this otherwise
effective in water, everything
exists, possible and it blows an
effective style of reconciling the requirement
of efficiency of values, the cyclist from
Novara and above all simple, we reconcile
performances between with the rest of the
Auxerre prison where nature to you,
presenting you this evening, which will
express themselves
in human forms, also the fate of
nature because the organizers of this debate
wanted to address sure shots and what I messed up
6 to 2 facing the turntables with you, the
answer, for example, by
exemplarity, the tinted exam, so
I will have the opportunity to present them to you at
greater length, you have here but
choices therefore represent so that Moody's,
while an exceptional personality,
an accent of this personal debate, forces
not only that to
professional success, on the contrary, participates
alongside his translator, seized at the bottom, that
then  Mr.
Vincent Segal's intervention is that of a personality
you double to know him and to
French fielders these seven and the training
and then you particularly need
communication and this didn't need
Jamie they have two cats in
question they communicate their plane
and he will want to forget
the elected officials of the forests those of the Quebecers
who
thank you
and so the tone
we see so via this day at the neckline to
Julien Guay thanked the partners
his confessions the Essonne press chamber
we also the general councilor of
the company
thank you for seeing but possible this
presentation thank you to all
the support which we will immediately apart from
the mourning the contributions of
this evening I am serene
simply because their sales are
carriers of Ciba their value
Yuji
ide daily these values ​​is dedicated to
reading is nicknamed black efficiency we
know that if it continues from
behind it is necessary so I ask
Mr. Jean Marc Brûlé for example his
nets no answer the young
Czech leaders and I say so I am
indeed their example subject salon
since the  CJD is an
association of
business leaders present throughout
France.
The principle of the movement, however, is that of a young
movement since
1938, and its founders originally aimed to
pass on a little bit, not too much,
or 10.9 and yesterday to the leaders of the
20th century with a lotion, society and other
evidence and very strong human qualities. Since
1938, for 72 years, the movement has been welcoming us.
We also represent 4,500
business leaders across the entire
national territory. The CJD, after a few
years, is also opening up
internationally with a presence in 9
countries
and representations in about
twenty countries and across all
continents. In their suitcases and what about the
center for young leaders
not very far away? Good evening. You must be
under 45 years old to be
elected. The checkerboard of financial contributions
and the luxury is really about sharing and
defending strong values. The
levels of the movement and training us for
another profession of entrepreneurial leader
or depositions of the certainties of the CJD
is to think that
the profession of leader is something
we are not naturally
competent in.  The profession of
entrepreneurial leader involves techniques that
can be acquired through
business school or elsewhere, but it's also learned, as we'll
see tonight, through the
practice of human relations, by
considering the value of this
idea. We call it overall performance, that is,
thinking that a
company isn't a monolith,
but rather a complex web of
different stakeholders:
its employees, shareholders,
customers, suppliers, and
civil society as a whole.
To achieve lasting and
sustainable success, it's important to
consider all these
parts. How do we
practice this approach? How does it
work
at the level of business leaders who
join us on this topic? It's wrong to say that you have to
take a step back. A
key problem for leaders is that they are
alone facing the company,
facing the world around them, facing
uncertainties about the present and
the future. Being able to exchange ideas freely and
confidentially with others is a real
strength in their daily lives. Two leaders
are their company,
so breaking free from their constraints is crucial.  Isolation,
taking a step back from the prevailing climate of
rigor, is already a first step, and then, following
training,
the CJB is not a movement
of employer demands, it is a
movement for training managers in
their role as managers, and to do this, the
training program focuses on three
things: training courses comprising 10
within the movement with
high-quality speakers who cover all
management topics in France, but also much more broadly,
notably interaction,
igniting a company. It's really the
slow pace of the
young managers' movements,
working groups that take place generally
dozens of times a year, bringing together about
ten young
managers, the internet is a key element, and they are
really focused on a particular theme, for
example, HR, for example, things
that are still relevant today,
how to
present the company
correctly on social networks, so we
really practice
daily work, ten times throughout
the year, plenary meetings for about
six months a year where the section
meets with
external speakers on various themes.
general and then
exceptional elements like tonight with what we call
in jargon maintaining
prestige, that is to say at a time when
the ground section is no longer focused on the
same section as the surrounding sections but
squarely on you, so people from
outside the movement on
high-quality themes, you will see that the
three speakers who really do
OS X proud will bring us a
human richness from my friend who shared in a
simple CJD and there it is a great moment
of meeting for the network from
outside and then of actor and
innovation to join me to grow
then in your role of
business development,
there you go, I am comfortable
saying that these ideas, I have a lot of
talk about local network at the local level,
the interview, local at the national level
since 4500 throughout France and
also regions and a national one, and
the national president, René
Mantel, notably with politicians,
always on the long term, know-how to assert, to
highlight the
CJD's long-term position of remaining
human in companies, so that they can
combine, not to say that the human is everything,
in any case, the phrase  The
foundation of the CJD is truly for an
economy at the service of humanity and
life, namely business, but not
business for the reader, respecting
human values ​​that are essential for
sustainable growth. Good evening. This is
the only important thing:
opening its doors to
employees and employers. When the Réseau
Entreprendre network was founded
105 years ago, the idea was
to offer employees... We have
an obligation when we are forced to
close two businesses.
We have an obligation to know
how we reintegrate people into the
economic world. In
the case where the person is
involved with these spiders, he was forced
to close... in Bidart, and when we
close later...
Céline... I want to put the skills at the service of
other entrepreneurs
to help them
respond, and thus we support them in
France. In France, you have been tempted by
the association for supporting business
creators and buyers
in the north, their position as leaders,
their questions as entrepreneurs... So it's
a movement that says... you
other vests... but you know
the navy... in this study  is important
to society, we, if reason, live
enormously because coming through
commitment, the minds tell me, we
invite you to come and discover it, it's hard,
you find it historically, thank you, thank you, there are
still words from Canada, it plans there
because it's these young people, 10 months
to finish,
if they want to anticipate tonight these
movements, finally put in place,
why not, because it's the
collective consciousness, of which nearly
300 times
Mr. Guy Children,
who spurs on 113, he graduated with
honors from the University of Lausanne, he
received the Presidential Medal
of Academics from the President of EADS,
rhymes with white, he spent 25 years in
a monastery, I'm going to tell you this
journey with a call that pushed him
to go out,
put into practice, had to take to
solidify in the United States, they see the
will, an SSD, all you
want, it's really that, avoids making him
a million from the
Croisette for Gladiator, appreciated,
he is today at a turnover of
200, 250,
radio voices, did or  If he was able to put in
place something truly safe, it's not the time for a
child's passion, and it's interesting
what he used. A leak from his
company was a refugee in the Senate. He
suffered a million online bets. I
will recall
the Indian farmer
if life upon
his departure.
He is the author of the work
in which, precisely, a
source of inspiration for
businessmen.
This gift will prove it to those present.
So we will spend some 30
with him
and its necessity. I wish, I wish,
I will adapt with
you, whether it relates to
his features on the day of
sharing
my experience of redoing
this match with you at the workshop.
I would first like to thank him
for creating this. Here I meet them and a
kata, and he then invited me,
and I was captivated.
And
then what theme in which to achieve breakthroughs?
I started traveling on 156 to
17, and Figo
denounces a small visit,
estimating the project in
service
is normal, and one box. There is a way
of
stable figures and
fiction
2,
and this for
purposes and a  dial by ordering to stop
the roof of the network go to the New York
Times and business starts in the
turnover business we want to see
as
we see you understood how it works
evoking
the forces but keep everything away in any
case
wait Madrid as in
trials for
business is business man Brad Pitt All
Blacks it's
having two clubs business my
mind Ares IX and
he told me I see if I can do
ethics in alignment and win
$1 million ahead
of sports
at each loop
the oldest
of the gusts and
Gemalto of
student pectins is what the
big
names
in mind
the sudden
rise
of New York bookmakers of asthma and to
Red Bull and
the body of Anne Caudal
and notebook explained m as
Batman the world
and I have homes all over the world
the essence of as towards money in
pebbles
and
in
the
six this
no people
who do
advances food position in case
of agreement
which
is funny
the dog
so
the
question
of places
Dominique Bargues and  Scott Wittman,
his party, which notions we have
well that Timothy and that it's a
family life according to what he put in money and
overpriced scam of spirit
Gollac 10 years of
and still care de
Gaulle in
Comines family at the caliphate
women and
families first made
the face of
a green
is not coming days his
family Desmarais
except maybe
wish to be informed that it comes from
me like that one
it works
at the
quay of Saint Paul
6 at
my place
a pen
contacts and
tech
the style where the go reigns
at
Cuba goes the Sea Dogs of St but I'll
skip and it's very trendy
other
examples
of pensions goes fast he is alive his
madam year
but just as much
of
Mamadou is a true enthusiast
in understanding this subject of security carried out
many
expectations have
given everything but the steak
of the deputies of the three of the cervicals is
certain there are 27 their
roofs of voice services and there is
a
gentleman per mm they
like  caressing the
five-year agreement
and even as if to be carried out
with reading in
Korhogo
after
each site with
two goals in five place settings and this
box click
here
it is the ionic one in May
and your
good and go in the
night are Zack
Snyder Pipitone
the
family Venza
in the world has a New York in
August an action carried out
with
techniques
at the end of the reign
of technical prowess
and a destiny of the technique if you
understand the same year
that is to say
studies
in
China yes break to the fiber have raised
Kikuku Didace in May according to Cameroon
who you like that
I have my question is
addressed
to the moon than by the bunker
like a lot of
trouble
to team B like that it's not
a small enclosure
Simon
if your
ideas his mandate of the furrow
we
have spent only succeeding difficult
in this
without being
spotted interventions are
also years
evening on a subject that
Plessis
J
in the hands
you
go to M
efficiency existence how to manage to
break the performance of our two
conferences around
iron that you have
seized  But if tomorrow quickly, and I was
very moved to hear
the conference on the prohibition of those
years who leave for me that I hear
with obviously a particular software,
it is that of the great capacity of
the human mind to be able to interpret the
name of different tracy where I will first go to
Vernet Cluny, so that there is a
link or when the thirst, the transition,
then I will try to define nine
angles where we will study the efficiency
according to francs, not to say a
keyword which is first an introduction
that must be made,
the power of the human mind has
always been central in
Western philosophy, and it is true that
we expect to direct them in
Western philosophy,
it is the side of an efficiency that will make itself
like master and possessor of
nature, a technical efficiency embodied
by cars, notably, therefore by a
French philosopher, and we are
often presented with Western philosophy as
being rationalist philosophy, where
precisely what we have just
heard seems quite exotic,
but the record has put
Western philosophy, which is extremely
exotic, between lummen, which comes
completely out of the  Rationalism 9.3
instrumental technique and which
obviously did not highlight this
current at all. Art is what I try
to embody. In philosophy, it's what we
call the finalist current, and
vitalism, we'll say to Alain, in the
middle of the 20th century, was totally
abandoned a year ago to embody
one recently, see by
Nietzsche, by Bergson, etc., and other
philosophers. No doubt a very, very
long